A Finding Aid to the Jamison Thomas Gallery Records, 1940-2000, bulk 1980-1995, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Jamison Thomas Gallery Records
1940-2000
bulk 1980-1995
Archives of American Art
Jamison Thomas Gallery
AAA.jamithog
Archival Resource Key
27.2 Linear feet
0.001 Gigabytes
The Jamison Thomas Gallery records measure 27.2 linear feet and 0.001 Gb and date from 1940-2000, with the bulk of the records dating from 1980-1995, reflecting the years the Gallery operated in Portland Oregon. About 1/2 of the records consist of artists' files of artists represented by the gallery and artists of interest. Also found are administrative records, client and collector files, financial and legal records, exhibition files, and publicity files.
Biographical / Historical
Jamison Thomas Gallery opened in Portland, Oregon in 1980 as the Folk Craft Gallery founded by William Jamison and Jeffrey Thomas. The gallery changed its focus and name in 1985 and began to specialize in contemporary photography, sculpture, and textile arts. Among the most notable artists represented by the gallery were Rick Bartow, Stuart Buehler, Dennis Cunningham, Susan Seubert, Dan May, Gus Van Sant, Ruza Erceg, Mark Bulwinkle, Jon Serl, Gregory Grenon, and Erik Stotik. Jamison Thomas Gallery closed in 1995, after William Jamison died from complications with AIDS.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into six series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Administrative Records, 1980-1996 (2.4 linear feet; Box 1-3)
Series 2: Client and Collector Files, 1980-1995 (4.5 linear feet; Box 3-7, 0.001 GB; ER01)
Series 3: Financial and Legal Records, 1980-2000 (2.8 linear feet; Box 7-10)
Series 4: Exhibition Files, 1975-1995 (2 linear feet; Box 12-12)
Series 5: Publicity Files, 1980-1996 (1.5 linear feet; Box 12-14)
Series 6: Artists' Files, 1940-1996 (14 linear feet, Box 14-28)
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is available in the Archives' Washington, D.C. research facility. Contact Reference Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Jamison Thomas Gallery records were donated to the Archives of American Art in 2001 by gallery director Charles Froelick.
Scope and Contents
The Jamison Thomas Gallery records measure 27.2 linear feet and 0.001 GB and date from 1940-2000, with the bulk of the records dating from 1980-1995, reflecting the years the Gallery operated in Portland Oregon. About 1/2 of the records consist of artists' files of artists represented by the gallery and artists of interest. Also found are administrative records, client and collector files, financial and legal records, exhibition files, and publicity files.
Among those represented in the artists' files are Robert Gilkerson, Gregory Grenon, Dan May, Jon Serl, Rick Bartow, Mark Bulwinkle, Jay Backstrand, Stuart Buehler, Mark Calderon, Baba Wague Diakite, and Gus Van Sant.
Sculpture; Photography; Textile crafts; Art galleries, Commercial -- Oregon; May, Dan; Jamison Thomas Gallery; Grenon, Gregory, 1948-; Diakité, Baba Wagué; Gilkerson, Robert, 1922-; Van Sant, Gus; Buehler, Stuart; Bartow, Rick, 1946-; Calderon, Mark; Bulwinkle, Mark, 1946-; Thomas, Jeffrey; Serl, Jon, 1894-1993; Backstrand, Jay, 1934-; Folk Craft Gallery (Portland, Or.)
- Administrative Records, 1980-1996; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2.4 Linear feet Boxes 1-3
  Scope and Contents
  Administrative records concern the founding and everyday business of Jamison Thomas Gallery. Materials include clippings, catalogs, general correspondence and mailing lists, notebooks, photographs, awards and recognitions, William Jamison's desk files, and membership files from various commissions and councils. Also included are files relating to events held at the gallery, including gallery rental fees, correspondence and invitation lists, and event programs.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - ACLU Oregon, Free Expression Award, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annex, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Art/AIDS, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Artists, Catalogs and Representation, 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cascade AIDS Project, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Charities and Auctions, 1981-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, Artists to be Considered, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Folkcraft Gallery and Artists, 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, Washington Folk Artists, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11-18)
  - Correspondence, Contribution Letters, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Thank You Letters, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Curator Selection Committee, Oregon Art Institute/PCVA, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Designers, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Farewell, William" Celebration Concert Honoring William Jamison, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Folkcraft Gallery Miscellaneous Prints/Negatives, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gallery Events, Miscellaneous, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Gallery Rental, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation Fellowship, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Mailing Lists, Artists and Galleries, circa 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - McKenzie River Gathering Foundation Benefit, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mehmet Memo Sander Dance Company, Support, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Metropolitan Arts Commission, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Names Project, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Folk Arts Program, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Letters to Congressmen, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - North Park Blocks, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Notebooks, 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Notebooks, circa 1989-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-7)
  - Oregon Arts Commission, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Oregon Governor's Arts Award, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pacific Northwest College of Art, Business of Art Course by Jamison, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Gallery Snapshots, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Portland State University Dance Benefit, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Prom on the Moon" Event, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Staff Notes, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Support Our Communities Political Action Committee Concert, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Washington State Arts Commission, 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17-19)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Art Issues, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Collection, 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Collectors Guide, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Correspondence, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Correspondence, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Correspondence, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3-6)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Correspondence, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Museum of American Folk Art, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Personal, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Photos, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - William Jamison Desk Files, Photos by Rebekah Johnson, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - William Jamison Memorial, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - William Jamison Roast, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Wyoming Arts Council, 1982-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
- Client and Collector Files, 1980-1995; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 4.5 Linear feet Boxes 3-7; 0.001 Gigabytes ER01
  Client and collector files document business transactions between the Jamison Thomas Gallery and various clients, collectors, and customers regarding the purchase of artwork, the transfer of artworks between locations for the purpose of consignment, or loans for exhibitions. Materials include loan and consignment agreement forms, purchase receipts and invoices, inquiries, photographs, and shipping notifications.
  Arranged as 3 subseries:
  Missing Title
  2.1: Galleries, Museums, and Schools, 1980-1995
  2.2: Individuals, 1980-1995
  2.3: Corporate, 1985-1995
  - Galleries, Museums, and Schools, 1980-1995; 2.1; Archival Resource Key
    Correspondence and business agreements with other galleries, museums, and schools. Included within this subseries are guilds and artist representatives, craft collecting organizations, and stores. The majority of files consist of correspondence received by the gallery, including exhibition cards and announcements. Also included are loan and consignment agreements, sales invoices for the gallery and for other organizations, and purchase documentation.
    - Alexander Gallery, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - The Allrich Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - American Indian Contemporary Arts Gallery, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - ArtBanque, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Artera, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Arthur Roger Gallery, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Arts of the Raven Gallery, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - At Home Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - The Bar and Diamond Gallery, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Bedford Gallery, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bellevue Art Museum, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Bentwood Furniture, 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Beyond Reason Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Blackfish Gallery, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - The Blue Sky Gallery, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Blue Sky, Oregon Center for the Photographic Arts, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Braunstein Gallery, 1985, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, Print Portfolio, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bruce Velick Gallery, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Buffalo Gallery, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Carl Hammer Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Carole Smith Gallery, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Catlin Gabel School, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cavin-Morris Gallery (Ethnographic Arts Inc.), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - C.E. Rynd Photographic Fine Arts, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Charles Cowles Gallery, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Cirrus Gallery, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Clark Gallery, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Clatsop Community College, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Cooper-Seeman Fine Arts, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Craft and Folk Art Museum, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Craftsmen's Guild of Mississippi, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Davidson Galleries, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Eastern Montana College, Northcutt-Steele Gallery, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Elijah Pierce Art Gallery, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Empire Gallery, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Esther Saks Gallery, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Eye of RA, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Foster-White Gallery, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Francine Seders Gallery, 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - G and W Antiques, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Gallery of Functional Art, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Gasperi Gallery, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28-30)
    - Graythorne Gallery, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Greg Kucera Gallery, 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hal Bromm, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Hampton Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Heard Museum, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Henry Art Gallery, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Himalaya Imports, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Hiram Butler Gallery, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Houston Center for Photography, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Hudson Northcross Gallery, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Interstate Firehouse Cultural Center, 1984, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Jan Baum Gallery, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Jan Cicero Gallery, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Jay Johnson Gallery, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Jennifer Pauls Gallery, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Jerome Evans Gallery, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Jill George Gallery, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Joan Robey Gallery, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - John Cusano Gallery, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - K.C. Folk Art Company, 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Karl Bornstein Gallery, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Kear's Broom Shop, 1982-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - King-Heller Gallery, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Lafayette Parke Gallery, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Left Bank, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Linda Durham Gallery, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lynn Goode Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lynn McAllister Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Mahabiak, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Mahafey Fine Arts, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Mahler Fine Arts, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Marianne Portlow Gallery, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Mark Moore Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Maryhill Museum of Art, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Marylhurst College, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Mather Gallery, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Maude Kerns Art Center, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Mia Gallery, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Missoula Museum of the Arts, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Mobilia Gallery, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Montgomery Museum of Fine Arts, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Museum of American Folk Art, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - New Orleans Museum of Art, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - New York Galleries, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21-22)
    - Newport Harbor Art Museum, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - North Carolina and East Coast Galleries, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - North Carolina Potters, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Oakland Museum, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Old Pueblo Museum, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Oneiros Gallery, 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Oregon Health Sciences University, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Oregon School of Arts and Crafts, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Oscarsson-Siegeltuch Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Pacific Northwest College of Art, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Phoenicia Designs, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Portland Art Museum, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Portland Community College Art Department, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - R.M. Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Radix Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - The Rainbow Man, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Rastetter Woolen Mill, 1981-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Read Stremmel Gallery, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Riverside Art Museum, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Robischon Gallery, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Rosa Esman Gallery, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Rutgers Barclay Gallery, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Sacred Circle Gallery of American Indian Art, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - San Francisco Craft and Folk Art Gallery, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - San Francisco Galleries, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Seattle Art Museum, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Seattle Galleries, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Seidman Gallery, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Shoshana Wayne Gallery, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Simpkins Gallery of Tribal Art, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Skagit Valley College, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Snyderman Gallery, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Southern Folk Potters, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - Splintworks, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Stewart Gallery, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stremmel Galleries, Ltd., 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Sunbird Gallery, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Susan Cummins Gallery, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Susan Duval Gallery, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Susan Whitney Gallery, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Tacoma Art Museum, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Tanaka Kimonos, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - TOPS Gallery, 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - University of Oregon, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - University of Washington Hospital, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Breier Gallery, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Wayne Martin, Inc., 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Western Washington University, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - White Bird Gallery, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - White Gallery, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - William Traver Gallery, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Wolff Gallery, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Yanagisawa Gallery, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Yao Design, 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Individuals, 1980-1995; 2.2; Archival Resource Key
    Correspondence and payment records with individual customers, curators, consultants, and collectors that frequented the gallery.
    - Becker, David, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER01 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - The Visionary Art of Rick Bartow: Works 1986-1992, Digital Documents, Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER01)
    - Berry, Karl, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Bolte, Gail, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Bronson, Albert, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Burger, Thea, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Cain, Candice, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Carcass, Johnny, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Chicago Clients, circa 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Ciz, Elizabeth, 1980-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Copilevitz, Mr. and Mrs. Louis, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Cowdery, Mr. and Mrs. C., 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Cumming, Elizabeth, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Davis, Jackie, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Douglas, John, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Dunn, Bob, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Efraimson, Darcy, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Efron, Jean, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Faust, Bob and Judy, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Freedman, Stephanie, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Gerena, Joseph G., 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Gerlach, Cynthia, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Gold, Donna, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Goldenberg, John, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Hess Collection, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Hoagland, Susan, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Wendy Wells, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Jacob, Mary Jane, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Norman and Lois, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Kahn, Bonnie, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Kangas, Linda and Gene, 1980-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Kay, Judy, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Kline, Steve, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Koch, Linda, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Kransen, Charon, circa 1980s-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)